<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MuscleApp</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open" translatable="false">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close" translatable="false">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Muscle Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="selamat_datang">Welcome in app Workout</string>


    <string name="w1">Workout at Home</string>
    <string name="w2">Workout First Brother</string>
    <string name="w3">Push Up</string>
    <string name="w4">Pull Up</string>
    <string name="w5">Sit Up</string>
    <string name="w6">Planking</string>
    <string name="w7">Cobra Pose</string>
    <string name="w8">Overhead Extension</string>
    <string name="w9">Chin Up</string>
    <string name="w10">Support Suplements</string>

    <string name="menu_home">Home</string>
    <string name="menu_gallery">Gallery</string>

    <string name="desc_image1">
    If you are planning to lose weight or have an ideal body shape,
    The easiest way you can do is to regularly do workout movements.
    </string>


    <string name="desc_image2">
    Workout can help the body burn calories and fat in a relatively short time.
    Not only that, workout is also another way if you don't like strenuous exercise.
    or just planning to start exercising regularly
    </string>

    <string name="desc_image3">
    Push ups are a type of strength exercise that works to train the biceps and triceps.
    </string>

    <string name="desc_image4">
    Pull ups are a form of strength training that aims to maintain and increase muscle mass.
    This exercise is beneficial for shaping the body, especially the muscles of the arms and upper body.
    </string>

    <string name="desc_image5">
    Sit ups are an exercise that has a variety of benefits, especially for toning the abdominal muscles so that they look flat.
    In addition to the abdominal muscles, this type of exercise can also help train the chest muscles
    </string>

    <string name="desc_image6">
    Planking is one of the most effective simple exercises for the body.
    Just by doing plank movements for 60 seconds every day,
    the muscles of the body will become strong and you will feel the benefits.
    </string>

    <string name="desc_image7">
    Cobra Pose is a powerful movement to improve posture, very effective in strengthening the spinal erector and muscles in other areas of the lower back.
    </string>

    <string name="desc_image8">
    The Overhead Extension, also known as the dumbbell tricep extension, is an isolation exercise that targets your triceps muscles.
    </string>

    <string name="desc_image9">
    Chin up is a weight training exercise that targets the latissimus dorsi muscles in the upper back,
    also the biceps muscles in the arm.
    </string>

    <string name="desc_image10">
    Whey supplements usually contain high protein and help build trained muscles.
    </string>
</resources>